[
    { "id": 1, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "El ciclón", "back": "Tornado" },
    { "id": 2, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La erupción volcánica", "back": "Volcanic eruption" },
    { "id": 3, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "El huracán", "back": "Hurricane" },
    { "id": 4, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La inundación", "back": "Flood" },
    { "id": 5, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La sequía", "back": "Drought" },
    { "id": 6, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "El incendio forestal", "back": "Forest fire" },
    { "id": 7, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "El maremoto", "back": "Tsunami" },
    { "id": 8, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La tormenta", "back": "Storm" },
    { "id": 9, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "Los relámpagos", "back": "Lightning" },
    { "id": 10, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La avalancha de nieve", "back": "Avalanche" },
    { "id": 11, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "Los truenos", "back": "Thunder" },
    { "id": 12, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "El terremoto", "back": "Earthquake" },
    { "id": 13, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La adolescencia", "back": "Adolescence" },
    { "id": 14, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La infancia", "back": "Infancy" },
    { "id": 15, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La juventud", "back": "Youth" },
    { "id": 16, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La madurez", "back": "Maturity" },
    { "id": 17, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La niñez", "back": "Childhood" },
    { "id": 18, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La vejez", "back": "Old age" },
    { "id": 19, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "El amor", "back": "Love" },
    { "id": 20, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "El íntimo", "back": "Close friend" },
    { "id": 21, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La amistad", "back": "Friendship" },
    { "id": 22, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La boda", "back": "Wedding" },
    { "id": 23, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La cita", "back": "Date" },
    { "id": 24, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "El divorcio", "back": "Divorce" },
    { "id": 25, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La luna de miel", "back": "Honeymoon" },
    { "id": 26, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "El matrimonio", "back": "Marriage" },
    { "id": 27, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "El noviazgo", "back": "Courtship" },
    { "id": 28, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "El novio", "back": "Boyfriend" },
    { "id": 29, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "Los novios", "back": "Couple" },
    { "id": 30, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La pareja", "back": "Couple" },
    { "id": 31, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "Los recién casados", "back": "Newlyweds" },
    { "id": 32, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La separación", "back": "Separation" },
    { "id": 33, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "Casado/a", "back": "Married" },
    { "id": 34, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "Comprometido/a", "back": "Engaged" },
    { "id": 35, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "Divorciado/a", "back": "Divorced" },
    { "id": 36, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "Separado/a", "back": "Separated" },
    { "id": 37, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "Soltero/a", "back": "Single" },
    { "id": 38, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "Viudo/a", "back": "Widowed" },
    { "id": 39, "category": "Vocabulario español", "front": "La novia", "back": "Girlfriend" }

  ]
  